<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AdmissionHelper</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="university_info">
        The University of Dhaka (Bengali: ঢাকা বিশ্ববিদ্যালয়, also known as Dhaka University or simply DU) is the oldest university in Bangladesh.
        Established in 1921 during the British Raj, it has made significant contributions to the modern history of Bangladesh.
         After the Partition of India, it became the focal point of progressive and democratic movements in Pakistan.
        Its students and teachers played a central role in the rise of Bengali nationalism and the independence of Bangladesh.
        It also enjoyed associations with Satyendra Nath Bose, Vijayaraghavan and Kazi Nazrul Islam.
        Today, it is the largest public research university in Bangladesh
        with a student body of 37,018 and a faculty of 1,992.
        It was identified by AsiaWeek as one of the top 100 universities in Asia. However, since the 1990s,
        the university has suffered from intensely politicized, partisan and violent campus politics promoted by Bangladesh\'s political parties.
    </string>
    <string name="university_info2">
        Motto :     শিক্ষাই আলো\n\n
        Motto in English\n\n
        Education is light\n\n
        Type:	Public university\n\n
        Established:	1921\n\n
        Chancellor:	Abdul Hamid\n\n
        Vice-Chancellor:	Md. Akhtaruzzaman\n\n
        Academic staff:  2,156\n\n
        Administrative staff:   3,887\n\n
        Students:	30,015\n\n
        Undergraduates:	23,620\n\n
        Postgraduates:	5,362\n\n
        Doctoral students:  764\n\n
        Other students:  269\n\n
        Location:	Dhaka, Bangladesh\n\n
        Campus:	Urban, 240 hectares (600 acres) (without the Institute of leather engineering and tech).
    </string>
    <string name="university_info3">
 This year, a total of 7,128 seats are available:\n\n
      1,750 under ‘Ka’ (Science) unit\n\n
      2,378 under ‘Kha’ (Arts) unit\n\n
      1,250 under ‘Ga’ (Business) unit\n\n
      1,615 under ‘Gha’ (combined) unit\n\n
  135 under the Fine Arts faculty.

    </string>
    <string name="rajUv1">The University of Rajshahi,
        also known as Rajshahi University or RU (Bengali: রাজশাহী বিশ্ববিদ্যালয়) is a public university
        which is the second largest university in Bangladesh, in Rajshahi, a city in northwestern Bangladesh.
        It was established in 1953, the second university to be established in what was then East Pakistan.
        The university is ranked third on the Bangladesh University Ranking 2017.
        The university\'s 59 departments are organised into ten faculties.
        Rajshahi University is in a 753 acres (3 km2) campus in Motihar,
        3 kilometres (2 mi) from the Rajshahi city centre. With 25,000 students and close to 1000 academic staff,
        it is one of the largest universities in Bangladesh.</string>
    <string name="rajUv2">
        Type:	Public\n\n
Established:	July 6, 1953\n\n
Affiliation:	University Grants Commission of Bangladesh\n\n
Chancellor:	President of Bangladesh\n\n
Vice-Chancellor:	M. Abdus Sobhan\n\n
Provost:	17 provosts\n\n
Pro Vice-Chancellor:	Professor Dr. Ananda Kumar Saha\n\n
Academic staff:   1,778 (December 2015)\n\n
Administrative staff: 2,258 (December 2015)\n\n
Students:	38,495 (December 2015)\n\n
Undergraduates:	15,258 (December 2015)\n\n
Postgraduates:	9,125 (December 2015)\n\n
Doctoral students: 2,112 (December 2015)\n\n
Location:	Rajshahi, Bangladesh\n\n
Campus:	Urban, 753 acres (3 km2)
    </string>
    <string name="rajUv3">www.ru.ac.bd</string>
    <string name="diu">Daffodil International University is a private university located in Dhanmondi, Dhaka, Bangladesh.
        It was established on 24 January 2002 under the The Private University Act of 1992. According to QS University Rankings: Asia 2019,
        DIU is a top-ranked private university among all the universities in Bangladesh.
        DIU is the first university in Bangladesh to have signed the UN\'s Commitment to Sustainable Practices of Higher Education Institutions.</string>
    <string name="diu1">
        Motto:	A Landmark to create the Future\n\n
Type:	Private\n\n
Established:	2002\n\n
Chairman:	Md. Sabur Khan\n\n
Chancellor:	Abdul Hamid, President of Bangladesh\n\n
Vice-Chancellor:	Prof. Dr. Yousuf Mahbubul Islam\n\n
Academic: staff719\n\n
Administrative: staff620\n\n
Students:	35,790\n\n
Undergraduates:	35,790\n\n
Postgraduates:	1,284\n\n
Location:	Dhaka, Bangladesh\n\n
Campus:	Urban 150 Acres\n\n
Affiliations:	UGC\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="diu2">www.daffodilvarsity.edu.bd
    </string>
    <string name="aiub1">
        American International University-Bangladesh, commonly known as AIUB is an accredited and renowned private university located at Kuratoli Road, Kuril in Dhaka, Bangladesh.
        The university is an independent organization with own Board of Trustees.
        It offers several degree programs at graduate and undergraduate level from four faculties, particularly in the field of engineering and business studies.
    </string>
    <string name="aiub2">

Established:	1994\n\n
Founder:	Dr. Anwarul Abedin\n\n
Chairman:	Ms. Nadia Anwar\n\n
Chancellor:	President of Bangladesh\n\n
Vice-Chancellor:	Dr. Carmen Z. Lamagna\n\n
Academic staff:  308 (full-time) as of Summer 2015-2016\n\n
Students:	100,00(approx) as of Spring 2016-2017\n\n
Location:	Dhaka, Bangladesh
    </string>
    <string name="aiub3">http://www.aiub.edu/</string>
    <string name="nsu1">
        North South University, also known as NSU is the first privately funded university in Bangladesh.
        Its business school is also the first in Bangladesh to receive American accreditation from the ACBSP in 2015.

The government of Bangladesh approved the establishment of North South University in 1992 under the Private University Act (PUA) 1992 (now replaced by PUA 2010).
        The university was formally inaugurated on 10 February 1993.

The North South University ranked 301-500 in the "Graduate Employability Ranking 2020" published by the higher education information service provider Quacquarelli Symonds (QS).
        The ranking indicates how well students from a university can gain a foothold on the global job market. This year (2019), NSU is among the top 2 in Bangladesh, and one of the top 500 universities on an international scale.
        The university ranked 301-350 in the "Asian University Rankings" published by QS World University Rankings.
        It is also ranked 1st among the private universities and 4th among all the universities in research output on the Bangladesh University Ranking 2019.

    </string>
    <string name="nsu2">

        Motto:	Center of Excellence in Higher Education\n\n
Type:	Private, research university\n\n
Established:	1992\n\n
Affiliation:	UGC\n\n
Chancellor:	 President of Bangladesh Abdul Hamid\n\n
Vice-Chancellor: 	Atique Islam\n\n
Academic staff: 907 (including 449 impermanent/adjunct faculty) (2015)\n\n
Administrative staff: 223 (2015)\n\n
Students:	13,990 (2015)\n\n
Undergraduates:	12,068 (2015)\n\n
Postgraduates:	1,922 (2015)\n\n
Location:	Dhaka, Bangladesh
    </string>
    <string name="nsu3">http://www.northsouth.edu/</string>
    <string name="aust1">
        Ahsanullah University of Science and Technology or commonly known as AUST first non-government engineering university to be established in Bangladesh.
        The University is considered as one of the finest engineering universities, the leading non-government engineering university in Bangladesh, which was founded by the Dhaka Ahsania Mission in 1995.
        Dhaka Ahsania Mission is a non-profit voluntary organization in Bangladesh.
        The Mission was established in 1958 by Khan Bahadur Ahsanullah.

    </string>
    <string name="aust2">
        Type:	Private Engineering University\n\n
Established:	1995\n\n
Chancellor:	 President Abdul Hamid\n\n
Academic staff:  350 (Year: 2014)\n\n
Administrative staff: 134 (Year: 2014)\n\n
Students:	6,843 (Year: 2014)\n\n
Undergraduates:	6,248 (Year: 2014)\n\n
Postgraduates:	575 (Year: 2014)\n\n
Location:	Dhaka, Bangladesh
    </string>
    <string name="aust3">http://www.aust.edu/</string>
    <string name="brac1">BRAC University (BRACU) is a private University in Bangladesh.
        It was founded as a branch of the BRAC organization by Sir Fazle Hasan Abed in 2001 under the Private University Act</string>
    <string name="brac2">
        Other name: BRACU\n\n
Motto:	Inspiring Excellences\n\n
Type:	Private\n\n
Established: 	2001\n\n
Chancellor:	 President Abdul Hamid\n\n
Vice-Chancellor:	Vincent Chang\n\n
Academic staff: 593 (2019)\n\n
Students:	9839 (2019)\n\n
Undergraduates:	8764 (2019)\n\n
Postgraduates:	1075 (2019)\n\n
Location:	Mohakhali, Dhaka, Bangladesh
    </string>
    <string name="brac3">https://www.bracu.ac.bd/</string>
    <string name="ju1">
        Jagannath University is a government-financed public university in Sadarghat, Dhaka, the capital of Bangladesh.
        Jagannath University is in the southern part of Dhaka city near the River Buriganga.
        In 1884, it was raised to a second grade college. Law was one of the first courses introduced.
        A common management committee administered the school and college until 1887, when the school section was separated to form the independent Kishore Jubilee School, now known as K. L. Jubilee School.
        The administration of the college was transferred to a board of trustees in 1907. In the following year, it became a first grade college.
    </string>
    <string name="ju2">
        Motto:	শিক্ষা, ঈমান, শৃঙ্খলা\n\n
Type:	Public\n\n
Established: 	20 October,2005\n\n
Chancellor: 	Abdul Hamid\n\n
Vice-Chancellor:	Mijanur Rahman\n\n
Academic staff:  960\n\n
Administrative staff:  850\n\n
Students:	17,134\n\n
Location:	Dhaka, Bangladesh
    </string>
    <string name="ju3">https://www.jnu.ac.bd/</string>
    <string name="jnu1">
        Jahangirnagar University is a public university in Bangladesh, based in Savar Upazila, Dhaka.
        It is one of the top and only fully residential[3] universities in Bangladesh.
        The university was established in 1970 by the Jahangirnagar Muslim University Ordinance of the government of Pakistan.
        Its first vice-chancellor, Mafizuddin Ahmed (PhD in chemistry, Penn State) took up office on 24 September 1970.
        The first group of students, a total of 150, were enrolled in four departments: Economics, Geography, Mathematics, and Statistics.
        Its formal inauguration was delayed until 12 January 1971, when the university was launched by Rear Admiral S. M. Ahsan, the chancellor.
    </string>
    <string name="jnu2">
        Type:	Public\n\n
Established:	1970\n\n
Chancellor: 	Abdul Hamid\n\n
Vice-Chancellor: 	Farzana Islam\n\n
Pro-Vice-Chancellor:	Md. Abul Hossain\n\n
Academic staff: 755 (2014)\n\n
Administrative staff: 1,700 (2014)\n\n
Students:	16,781(2014)\n\n
Undergraduates:	14,560(2014)\n\n
Postgraduates:	3,501 (2014)\n\n
Doctoral students: 2,274 (2014)
    </string>
    <string name="jnu3">http://www.juniv.edu/</string>
</resources>
